

## LÉON WALRAS MOURA DA SILVA

#### MOBILE DEVELOPER

Rua José Vieira dos Santos, 525 Sumaré, São Paulo, Brasil +55(84)99604-8195 leongdev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/leonwalras0

# TECHNOLOGICAL PROEFICIENCIES

- Unity 3D | C#
- Blender
- React Native
- XCode
- Adobe After Effects
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop



## UNITY + GDC STUDENT | 2018 SCHOLARSHIP

One of the 50 students selected around the globe for the Unity Student Scholarship to GDC 2018.

### SUMMARY

Degree in Digital Games at Potiguar University of Rio Grande do Norte (UNP), I've been working at the Video Game Industry since 2015, primarily as a generalist Game Developer, making cross industry projects, serous games and advergames at the mobile industry. Currently I'm working as React Native developer at IES2 - Inovação, Educação e Soluções Tecnológicas, focused on iOS.

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

React Native

Swift

Javascript

C#

• Redux

Unity 3D

3D Modelling

Lottie Animations

Drinking Coffee

### EDUCATION

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF RIO GRANDE DO NORTE	2011-2014
Science and Technology focused on computer engineering	*Uncompleted
POTIGUAR UNIVERSITY OF RIO GRANDE DO NORTE	2016-2018
Digital Games Degree	*Completed
EDMOND AND LILY SAFRA INTERNATIONAL	2018-2019
INSTITUTE OF NEUROSCIENCE	*Uncompleted
Master's program in Neuroengineering	·
<b>^</b>	

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**INTERAGE** 2014-2016

Programmer and Animator

Was an amazing experience, I've started as a 2D animator but, as the market changed, I had to learn how to adapt fast and develop new abilities. This company also was my gateway to the video games industry.

## SELF EMPLOYED Programmer, Game Developer

2016-2017

2020

After Interage I've decided to focus on Game Development. I've started working as a freelance, had the opportunity to work on cross industry projects (Mixed Reality), serious games and Advergames [Wayne's burger, Angry at School, Brinkids, Cidade Gentil (Gentil Negócios, O Boticário, Swarovski, Quem disse Berenisse)].

**POCKET LHAMA** 2017-2018

Programmer

Pocket Lhama is a small indie game studio from California, I worked remotely as a programmer on a project called Toasty. Was my first internacional job, is really amazing be able to interact with people around the world.

#### **MASSIVE WORK** 2018-2019

Game Designer

Worked as Game Designer, focused on mobile F2P projects. Was my first job as Full Game Designer and was an incredible experience, I've learned how hard could be communicate game design ( is really challenging). Learned about creative and collaborative processes and how to be a Jedi on Excel. I learned about people, communication, planning and eventually how to design better experiences.

#### IES2 - Inovação, Educação e Soluções Tecnológicas

React Native Programmer (Native iOS)

I'm currently working as a React Native developer and it's been an exciting experience. I'm connecting all my background with animations and interactive experiences and using those skills to build a state of the art products.